

Front-End Developer UI Designer



# +36 70 212 5929



iuga.laura.katalin@gmail.com



lauraiu.github.io/portfolio/



1147 Budapest (GMT+1)



in linkedin.com/in/laura-iuga

## ABOUT ME

I'm a Front-End Developer with design skills open to explore new experiences working for or with You! I'm enthusiastic to discover and learn new features and frameworks, to be involved in new projects. Thanks to my background in artistic field I keep implementing the ideadesign-functionality twist in work. As Frontend Developer my creativity, abstract thinking and detail oriented working manner are my strengths.

At the present I'm co-working like Front-End developer and designer in an Open-Source Project for Speech-to-Text and Searchable Audio Archive.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

(before "carrer change")

### DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER

HRP Europe Kft. | Dec 2019 - Aug 2021

- I was responsible for the company B2B newsletters by delivering the content (copywrited, designed, code it in HTML) and send it to 5k partners.
- Designed and coded new newsletter template for Outlook automated letters.
- Content writer for the company's sites. Ex.: SmartHome

## DIGITAL ARCHIVIST

Forum Hungaricum Nonprofit Kft. | Sept 2018 - Dec 2019

• Employed by Forum Hungaricum, I was working for the National Evangelical Collection and Archive. Besides scanning "old" documents, I was responsible for the correct OCR on archive text records, also upload them to the database for public access. MaNDA

#### MOTION PICTURE AND ANIMATION TEACHER

Szinapszis School - Nat. Qual. Reg. | 2015 March - Aug

• I teached for adults the basic animation and motion picture techniques like object animation, paper-cut and stop-motion animation.

### PROJECT COORDINATOR, ANIMATOR, GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Lemma Cultural Association - "Time Capsule" and "Island of Delights"

• I was the concept owner, coordinator and organizer of the projects made at Sziget Festival - NGO Island. The 3-days workshops/ performances involved 108 participants in 2013 and 240 in 2014. Island of Delights | Time Capsule

#### FREELANCER & CO-WORKER 2023 - 2009

· designed and made static HTML web pages, graphic designs, illustrations

## SKILLS

- · Front-End Coding
- Web Design
- · Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Problem-Solving
- Strong Communication
- HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript
- React | Github
- · VsCode, Figma, Canva
- · I'm patient, detail focused and flexible. Multitasking, capability to visualize ideas, perceptivity, empathy and criticism are my best, overthinking and perfectionism are my worst characteristic.

# EDUCATION

#### Codecool

Junior Front-End Developer Aug 2021 - Jan 2022

## Hungarian University of Fine Arts

Media Artist Master 2001 - 2007

# LANGUAGES

- Hungarian Mother tongue
- English Intermediate
- · Romanian Advanced
- French Conversational